Guide to the Dorothy Sarnoff papers, 1920-1998.
Sarnoff, Dorothy Papers, 1920-1998
- Series II. Singing Career
  - F. Recordings
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Singing on Jane Pickens Show, WRCA, June 16, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Softly, As in a Morning Sunrise, Woolworth Hour, Oct 28, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Sweetheart, ca. 1956 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Small Silver Voice Record (personal message record) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Plaza Persian Room - Dorothy Sarnoff and the Ray Bloch Orchestra: I Wish You Love/ Happiness, Softly, Feb 19, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on This is Show Business, May 16, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Kiss of Fire & Shall We Dance on Arthur Murray Party, Apr 12, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Segment on Tonight, June 11-12, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Arthur Murray Party, Apr 12, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Norman Black Orchestra on Out of This World,(D.S. vocal), Apr 24, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff singing on The Jane Pickens Show, June 16, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Street Scene, sides 1 & 3, Hollywood Bowl, July 17, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Street Scene, sides 2 & 4, Hollywood Bowl, July 17, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Street Scene, sides 5 & 7, Hollywood Bowl, July 17, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Street Scene, sides 6 & 8, Hollywood Bowl, July 17, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Singing, WRCA, June 2, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Stars for Defense, June 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - This Land is Mine & Make Someone Happy, Cerebral Palsy Telethon WOR-TV, Jan 14, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Hebrew Music not recorded by Dorothy Sarnoff (16 records) (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Carnegie Hall Broadcast I Have a Bonnet Trimmed With Blue/Air Di Bijou, May 23, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Saturday Night Revue, sides 1 & 3, Apr 8, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Saturday Night Revue, sides 2 & 4, Apr 8, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff as Nina in Friml's Firefly, sides 1 & 3, Dec 4, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff as Nina in Friml's Firefly, sides 2 & 4, Dec 4, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff as Nina in Friml's Firefly, sides 5 & 7, Dec 4, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff as Nina in Friml's Firefly, sides 6 & 8, Dec 4, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Showtime, U.S.A., side 1, Apr 8, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Showtime, U.S.A., side 2, Apr 8, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on This is Show Business, Apr 29, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Celebrity Time, May 20, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Toast of the Town singing It Must Be Wonderful / I've Got My Love to Keep Me Warm, Nov 3, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff, Feb 25, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff, Feb 25, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Toronto Symphony Pops - Dorothy Sarnoff Faust Aria / Just A Kiss, Apr 16, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Toronto Symphony Pops - Dorothy Sarnoff, Apr 16, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Mary Anne / Lover Come Back To Me, Chicago Theater of Air, May 22, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Wanting You / Lover Come Back To Me, Chicago Theater of Air, May 22, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Give Me One Hour, CBS, June 6, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Excerpts, ABC, Jan 20, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Radio Carabins, parts 1 & 3, Mar 23, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Radio Carabins, parts 2 & 4, Mar 23, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - The Desert Song, WNBC, Dec 12, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - The Desert Song, WNBC, Dec 12, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - The Desert Song, WNBC, Dec 12, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Comin Thru The Rye / Jurame (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Comin Thru The Rye / Jurame (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Bellatella / Jewel Song (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Woman's Song (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Jewel Song (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Unmarked (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Songs My Mother Taught Me / Il est Doux, Il est Bon, Recorded at Cornell University (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Gia il Sole Dal Gange / Stornellata Marinara, Recorded at Cornell University (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Ah Love But a Day (encore #1) / My Laddie (encore #2), Recorded at Cornell University (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Emerald Song / Lost (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Hymn Chorale / Forbidden Orchid (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Signs Are Brighter Than They Were Ever Before / Fiesta (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Unmarked (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Joshua Pierce, pianist (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8299)
    - D. S. songs (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8300)
    - "The Old Maid and the Thief, 1939 (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8301)
    - Ed Sullivan Show: "Shall We Dance" 1955 (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8301)
    - "Something Wonderful," "Kiss of Fire," "Shall We Dance," "I Wish You Love," "Happiness," "Softly," "Mia Patria," "One Kiss," "Czardas," "Toujours" (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8302)
    - "Something Wonderful," "Kiss of Fire," "Shall We Dance," "I Wish You Love," "Happiness," "Softly," "Mia Patria," "One Kiss," "Czardas," "Toujours" (c. 1-2) (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8303)
    - "Something Wonderful," "Kiss of Fire," "Shall We Dance," "I Wish You Love," "Happiness," "Softly," "Mia Patria," "One Kiss," "Czardas" (c.1-2) (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8304)
    - "Something Wonderful," "Kiss of Fire," "Shall We Dance," "I Wish You Love," "Happiness," "Softly," "Mia Patria," "One Kiss," "Czardas" (c.1-4) (Box 39, Audiocassette tr8305)
  - G. Photographs and Art
    - Dorothy Sarnoff, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - NBC - The Old Maid and the Thief, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Pagliacci, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Faust, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Headshot on piece of music from Die Fledermaus, 1942, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Opera Auditions of the Air, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Promotional Photograph, ca. 1942, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Rosalinda, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 28-31)
    - Rosalinda, 1942, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
    - Color pages of D.S. in Rosalinda, "Esquire" magazine 1942 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Maytime, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - New Moon, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Desert Song, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3-35)
    - Desert Song, 1945, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff in Los Angeles, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Tosca, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Waldorf - 1st Supper Club Show, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Faust, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - La Boheme, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Vagabond King, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Vagabond King, 1946, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
    - CBS Family Hour, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Heitor Villa-Lobos, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Shep in Central Park (from newspaper), 1948 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Magdalena Negative, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Magdalena, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Magdalena, 1948, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 12-13)
    - Various photographs of Dorothy Sarnoff, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 46-48)
    - Dorothy with Santa & Children - from Howard S. Cullman, NYC Port Authority Chairman - 1949 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Drawing of Dorothy Sarnoff by M. Task, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Great Waltz, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - New Moon, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Various photographs of Dorothy Sarnoff, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1959 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Promotional/Studio Photographs, ca. 1950-1959, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 18-20)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Eleanor Roosevelt, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - King and I, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 55-57)
    - King and I, 1951, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - King and I makeup chart, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Park Row, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Photographs for magazine, 1952, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 15-17)
    - Sam Fuller, autographed, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - USO Shows, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 59-60)
    - Cinderella Ball, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff at Stork Club, ca. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Ceil Chapman and Jerome Jennings, ca. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Mrs. Henry J. Heinz II, ca. 1953 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Forrest Tucker and others, ca. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Sam Grady, ca. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Event, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Paula Irene, autographed, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Eleanor Roosevelt, ca. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Ezio Pinza and others, ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Harry Hershfield and Jane Pickens, ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Ed Sullivan Show, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Gilbert Miller, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff at event, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Cornelius Ryan, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff with Rossano Brazzi, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff poster at Americana Hotel - Miami, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Promotional/Studio Photographs, ca. 1960-1969, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 22-24)
    - Merry Widow, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on stage, ca. 1963 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Publicity Photographs, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Drake Hotel Chicago Supper Club Act, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Poster for Persian Room show, ca. 1963, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Promotional Photograph, 1963, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on stage, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff at fashion show, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Bitter Sweet (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Claire Ellis (aka Clarissa), autographed (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Csardas Princess (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Drawing of D.S. signed "Pierot - NY Post" (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Ed Sullivan, autographed (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Emmerich Kalman, autographed, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Florence Easton, autographed (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Giacomo Vaghi (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Gian Carlo Menotti, autographed (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Hedda Hopper, autographed, Oversized (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Heitor Villa Lobos, autographed (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Jan Peerce, autographed (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - La Boheme (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Lawrence Tibbett, autographed (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Mary Martin, autographed (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Miscellaneous Publicity Photographs (Box 5, Folder 97-119)
    - Miscellaneous Show and Event Photographs (Box 5, Folder 90-96)
    - Oscar Karlweis, 2 Photographs, 1 autographed (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Ralph Herbert, autographed (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Ralph Morgan, autographed (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Rosarita, autographed (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Sterling Holloway, autographed (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Unidentified female, autographed (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Unidentified female, autographed (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Unidentified male, autographed (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Unidentified male, autographed (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - H. Ephemera and Miscellany
    - Cup from Presby Laurence Society, 1920 (Box 4)
    - Cow bell from Magdalena, 1948 (Box 4)
    - Cymbal (Box 4)
    - Framed newspaper caricature of Dorothy Sarnoff in Magdalena, 1948 (Box 4)
    - Framed newspaper caricature of Dorothy Sarnoff with costar in Magdalena, 1948 (Box 4)
    - 1948-1949 Celebrity Service Contact Book (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Small binder with Song Lists, ca. 1949 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - "Youth Oscar" from Youth United, 1949 (in 2 pieces) (Box 4)
    - Kazoo (Box 4)
    - Metal plate engraved "Miss Dorothy B. Sarnoff" (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous song lists, notes, and itineraries (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Small notebook with Lyrics (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Sound box (Box 4)
    - Stick percussion instrument (Box 4)
    - White Sequined Dress (Box 4)
    - Appointment books 1956 1961 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - D. S. on Ed Sullivan Show (c.1-VHS, c.2-3 [VHS]) 1956 1995 (Box 39, Video V-1501)
    - Carnegie Hall Gala with Boston Symphony Orchestr, Seiji Ozawa (1-VHS) n.d. (Box 39, Video V-1502)
- Series III. Speech Career
  - A. Correspondence
    - Questions from Speech Dynamics Students, 1971-1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Nathan, Dan? (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Ogilvy, David (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Luv Letters, 1957-1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Collier, Diana (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - [Herzig?], Philip (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - [Jacak?], Pam (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - [Johndroe?], M. Elizabeth (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - [Nadine G.] (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - [Tougvla?], Kay (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Albert, Harold (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Aucello, Mae D. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Ball, G. Carl (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Bartter, Scharlie W. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Belmuth, Leona (Mrs. Nat) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Berlin, Gail Joyce (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Biedler, Betty (Mrs. Ashby Lee) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Blanck, Gertrude (signed "Trudy") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Carrillo, Hazel E. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Cartelli, Louis V. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Chen, C.Y. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Chester, Winifred (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Clagett, Dorothy Tirrell (Mrs. Page B.) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Coiner, Lewis M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Collins, George (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Connolly, William J. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Cousins, Norman (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Culver, George (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - de Mare, George (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Dodson, Joseph A. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Donovan, Marguerite (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Doran, William M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Dover, Alice F. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Dubin, Mary (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Eckley, Mary (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Eckley, Mary (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Engel, Carolyn (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Epstein, Eleni (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Esses, Leo (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Farber, Leon (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Farker, Idabelle (Mrs. Wilson) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Feinstein, Melvin (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Foont, Paul J. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Ford, John C. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Frumkin, Paul (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Gareis, Don H. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Garson, Bunny (signed "B.&A.) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Gaul, Emmy Lou (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Gertshore, Janice (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Gildermeister, Richard (signed "Dick") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Gleik, Virginia (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Gordon, David Cole (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Greene, James L. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Griffith, Ninette (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Harding, Stephen (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Hart, Brian (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Henry, Martha (Mrs. Jerome) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Holmes, Leah M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Hunt, Ann C. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Husby, Milt (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Irwin, Patricia Marie (Pat) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Jones, Barbara (Mrs. Bernard C.) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Kennedy, William P., D.D.S. (signed "Phil") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - King, Wilma V. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Kittrell, Righard J. (signed "Dickie") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Klos, Louis A. (signed "Lou") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Kupcinet, Irv (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Laise, Carol C. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Laliberte, Mimi (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Lane, G.P. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Lee, Helen (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Lifson, Mrs. Michael A. (signed "Eva") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Luper, Oral L. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Malmer, Reynold W. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Manson, Mrs. Elmer K. (signed "Manie?") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - McAdams, Kathy (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - McCurdy, W.F. (signed "Bill") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Meador, Margaret (Mrs. Carl Wise) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Merrill, Esther (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Miller, Jane (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Nachem, Rita (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Newman, Jeremy U. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - November, Jo (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Obler, Mimi (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - O'Boyle, Janet (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - O'Flaherty, Mrs. William A. (signed "Barbara") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Peeler, E.D. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Pixley, Ida Lee (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Podell, Judy Rothenberg (Mrs. Robert) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Rabb(?), Sheila (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Ramona (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Risberg, Olivia (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Risberg, Olivia (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Rose, Duke J. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Rowe, Joan (Mrs. Lee) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Rudd, Lee (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Russell, Ralph E. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Saar, Mindy (and John) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Sand, Barry (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Schmitz, Helen (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Sgromolo, Irene (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Shohet, Ruben (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Smith, Frank W. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Sogg, Barbara (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Spanier, M. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Steffey, Wayne (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Stein, Jeffrey Alan (signed "Jeff") (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Stevenson, Adlai E. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Thompson, Eve Lloyd (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Twentyman, Esther F. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Walter, Dick (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Walters, Barbara (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Waters, Eleanor C. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Weinstein, Joyce (Mrs. Robert S.) (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - West, Jo (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Widener, Ralph W., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Yoken, Melvin B. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Youpa, Don (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Zercher, Tom (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Luv Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - [Beverly] (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - [Byron?], Jackie (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - [Conrad?] (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - [June] (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - [Klasen?], Nancy (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - [Syrmolo?], Irene (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Allen, Audrey (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Arnold, Gale (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Bachrach, Charles L. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Bandler, Ned W., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Biel, Alexander L. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Brigish, Alan P. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Brooks, Joseph E. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Burger, Chester (signed "Chet") (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Burkat, Iris (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Buteau, June D. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Carrey, Susan (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Clark, Brian G. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Cohn, John L. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Coiner, Lewis M. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Cole, Lawrence R. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Cook, Bruce (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Cooper, Winston L. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Couch, Patricia (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Cummings, Robert L. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Curran, R.T. (signed "Ted") (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Davis, Joel (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Dickman, Carol (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Doorley, [Carl?] A. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Dowling, William O. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Dowling, William Q. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Evans, Richard (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Finell, Alyce (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Gale, Bill (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Gitt, Patricia (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Grebla, Len (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hamilton, Pat (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Harun, Joseph S., M.D. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hawes, Donald K. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hill, James F. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hilsinger, A.R. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hodgetts, H. Leonard (signed "Len") (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hopkins, Thomas Hollis (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Howatson, Marianne (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hoyle, Ross S. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hunt, Cathi (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hurwitz, Robert S. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Hyland, Robert (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Johnson, Tod (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Kampen, Irene (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - King, Terry D., M.D. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Kirshbaum, Carolyn (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Klass, Phyllis (Mrs. Felix) (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Kleiner, Sanford (signed "Sandy") (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Klenicki, Rabbi Leon (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Klepper, Anna (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Knowlton, A[rha?] O. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Lampl. Dave (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Levine, Phil (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Levine, Phil (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Lowry, Judith (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Lund, John (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - MacDonald, Angus N. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - MacNeil, Robert (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - McFann, William C. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - McGreevy, Becky (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - McMullan, Paul W. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - McMullan, Paul W. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Millell, Lita (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Miller, Angela (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Moran, John A. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Murphy, Thomas S. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Nacinovich, Anthony J. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - O'Neill, Henry M. (signed "Butch") (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Paetro, Maxine (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Pepper, Murray and Nancy (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Prange, Vincent (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Pulitzer, Sidney (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Rockwell, Don (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Rosham, Chuck (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Roth, June L (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Seidel, Bob (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Sherman, William (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Slater, David B. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Socimara, Eriberto and Manita (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Sullivan, Humphrey (signed "Sull") (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Turco, Thomas F. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Watts, Cleal T., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Weiss, Donald (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Weissman, Robert E. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Whitcomb, Meg (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Williams, Marty (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Willner, Catherine (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Wolf, Jeanne (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Wooters, Kathi (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Yu, Gloria (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Luv Letters, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - [Hands?], Venetia (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Abell, Bess (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Anderson, Barbara (Mrs. Robert O.) (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Anton, Mark J. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Barner, Edward L. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Becker, Stephanie L. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Bell, Vincent G., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Benson, James (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Bernhard, Henry P. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Biklen, Paul (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Boggs, W. Dixon (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Boyce, Virginia S. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Bracken, Joseph R., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Braun, D.K. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Buck, Carol J. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Carroll, Thomas S. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Chiles, L.M. (signed "Bud") (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Christie, Tom E. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Cole, Lawrence R. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Dalbey, Stephen I. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Dowling, William G. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Dreman, David (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Elliott, John, Jr. (signed "Jack") (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Emmett, Martin (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Evans, Richard (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Fiorelli, Anthony J., Jr. (Box 21, Folder 17)